talkwalker.com 2018-12-20

# Privacy Policy - Talkwalker

### Privacy Policy

1\. INTRODUCTION  

The terms and conditions of this privacy policy (hereinafter the “Privacy Policy”) apply to all Services that Licensee may subscribe to under Talkwalker’s Terms of Service (available at: www.talkwalker.com/en/terms-of-service/).  In this Privacy Policy, all capitalized terms shall have the same meaning as set forth in the Terms of Service, unless otherwise stated.  

For the purpose of providing the Services and Trial Services, Talkwalker collects personal data within the following conditions.  Licensee expressly agrees that it has read this Privacy Policy carefully, that it has understood its meaning and is thus perfectly informed of and expressly accepts its content.  

2\. DATA COLLECTED  

When Licensee creates an Account in order to use the Talkwalker Free Search Service and/or Trial Services, Talkwalker asks Licensee to provide contact information such as name, first name, telephone number, e-mail address, company name of Licensee, etc.  When Licensee acquires Services, additional information will be requested from Licensee by Talkwalker such as billing information and address.  

In this Privacy Policy, the personal data as mentioned above are referred to as “Licensee’s Personal Data” or “Its Personal Data”. Talkwalker may also collect personal data of users surfing on Talkwalker’s websites such as these users’ IP addresses.  

3\. USE OF DATA  

3.1  Purpose  

Talkwalker uses the personal data collected for the following purposes:  

  * Identification and authentication of Licensee when Licensee accesses its Account;  
  * Providing the Services to Licensee;  
  * Billing purposes; 
  * Improving the quality of the Services provided;  
  * Market research purposes;  
  * Marketing and advertising purposes in the conditions set out in Article 5 below.  

Third-Party Platforms may collect personal data concerning Licensee if Licensee connects to such Platforms via the Services. Talkwalker is not responsible for the manner in which these Platforms handle any personal data that may be disclosed to them. Licensee is invited to refer to the appropriate Third-Party Platform’s privacy provisions in order to verify how its personal data is used by such Platforms.  Talkwalker’s Services provide URL links towards third-party websites. Talkwalker is not responsible for the manner in which these third-party websites handle any personal data that may be disclosed to them. Licensee is invited to refer to the appropriate third-party website’s privacy policy in order to verify how its personal data is used by such third-party website.  

3.2  Transfers of data  

Licensee’s Personal Data will not be shared with third parties, except as provided below.  Talkwalker may resort to subcontractors that are located outside the territory of Luxembourg for Service optimization purposes.  In this context, Talkwalker may resort to:  \- Subcontractors located in the United States solely for the purposes of providing Talkwalker with client relationship management services and marketing and  emailing services;  \- Subcontractors located in the European Union for the purpose of providing Talkwalker with payment services.  

4\. COOKIES  

Talkwalker uses cookies in order to better understand how its applications and websites work and to to optimize the online and mobile experience for the customer. Please refer to our Cookie Policy for more details on how we process Cookies.  

5\. MARKETING PREFERENCES  

Talkwalker may use Licensee’s Personal Data to contact Licensee to discuss the Services it has subscribed to or to send Licensee information concerning Talkwalker and/or the Services and/or promotional activities via newsletters, messages, calls and letters to the e-mail address, telephone number or postal address provided by Licensee.  By accepting this Privacy Policy, Licensee thus expressly accepts that Talkwalker uses the e-mail address, telephone number or postal address provided by Licensee in order to contact Licensee for the purposes above.  Except as mentioned in this Privacy Policy, Talkwalker does not use Licensee’s Personal Data for any other kind of marketing or promotional purposes.  Licensee’s may opt out of being contacted by Talkwalker at any time by using the opt-out link provided in any newsletter sent to Licensee or by contacting Talkwalker in this regard at the following e-mail address: contact[at]talkwalker.com  

6\. RIGHTS OF LICENSEE  

Licensee can update or correct any of Its Personal Data at any time by contacting Talkwalker at the following e-mail address: contact@talkwalker.com.  Licensee is entitled to request Talkwalker to provide Licensee, free of charge, with a list of all of Licensee’s Personal Data stored by Talkwalker by sending an e-mail in this regard to the following e-mail address: contact@talkwalker.com. Talkwalker undertakes to provide Licensee with such list within a reasonable timeframe.  

7\. YOUR RIGHTS  

Under GDPR you have the following rights:

  * The right to request access your data,
  * The right to request that your data is updated or rectified,
  * The right to request that we refrain from further use of your personal data
  * The right to request that your personal data is deleted.

To exercise any rights listed above, please email us at [dpo@talkwalker.com](mailto:dpo@talkwalker.com), or write to us at the address listed at the top of this document.

We will handle all requests in a timely manner but we may in our discretion ask for additional information in order to confirm your identity.

We may not always be able to immediately remove all your personal data, for example, if the law requires us to keep such data (e.g. for compliance or legal retention purposes).

We will do our best to execute your requests. If we do not handle the requests in line with your expectations, you also have the right to file a complaint with National Commission for Data Protection, our data privacy authority (<https://www.cnpd.lu/>), about the processing of your data under this Author Privacy Policy. In case of a breach, you can also file a complaint with the local authority on data privacy in the country where you reside.

8\. MISCELLANEOUS  

This Privacy Policy shall be governed and construed in accordance with the laws of the Grand-Duchy of Luxembourg. The courts of the judicial district of Luxembourg-City have exclusive jurisdiction in relation to any dispute arising out of or in relation with this Agreement.  

Talkwalker may alter terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy, in whole or in part, by  notifying Licensee of such alterations beforehand via an appropriate method of information .
